Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; 3; 3350
  - Athletics, 2004 October 10-2016 April 22; 3.1; 3350
    - Media & Marketing: take shot of Hall of Fame trophy for web site, meet Brian DePasquale at 4:30 on 10/10/07., 2007 October 24; 24.8 MB 10
    - Media & Marketing: 10/15/07 at 3:30 in studio to take shots of two athletic trophies., 2007 October 29; 64.9 MB 22
    - Media and Marketing: 2/2/08 @ 7:00 pm SEFCU Arena Big Purple Growl 2008, 2008 February 4; 280.4 MB 58
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/8/08 @ 10:00 am for "older men basketball" at the SEFCU Arena., 2008 April 8; 127.2 MB 63
    - AAU Karate National_opening ceremony, 2008 July 2; 40.9 MB 96
    - Coach Bob Ford, 2008 August 6; 12.8 MB 24
    - new locker room, 2008 October 3; 54.3 MB 60
    - Hall of Fame_08, 2008 October 25; 76.3 MB 162
    - SEFCU sign unveiling, 2009 May 13; 18.9 MB 5
    - womens soccer trophy, 2009 September 1; 18.8 MB 9
    - Hall_Fame, 2009 October 10; 277.0 MB 260
    - Hall_Fame, 2009 October 10; 277.0 MB 260
    - Hall of Fame Ceremony, 2010 October 8; 101.5 MB 224
  - Athletics Portraits, 2014 March 3-2014 December 12; 3.2; 132
    - Media and Marketing: 5/4/05 @ 3 PM RACC Arena Josh Tangney / student athelete digital, 2005 May 16; 240.7 MB 163
    - Sports Information: 1/30/08 @ 2:30 PM studicle Women's Lacrosse / Trisha Primomo, 2008 February 12; 1.8 MB 8
    - student athletes_Cushing_Reynolds, 2009 January 24; 13.8 MB 33
    - Joe Reardon_softball, 2009 February 5; 18.4 MB 31
    - Kevin Galuski, 2009 March 31; 59.9 MB 36
  - Baseball, 2013 September 6-2013 September 9; 3.3; 56
  - Field Hockey, 2013 October 18-2013 November 19; 3.4; 40
    - Sports Information: 11/18/04 @ 4 PM Main Gym Bleechers Team photo: Women's Field Hockey digital, 2004 December 3; 16.6 MB 10
  - Football, 2012 April 6-2015 September 14; 3.5; 802
    - Sports Information: 5/16/03 @ 2 PM Studio Football players digital, 2003 May 30; 8.8 MB 18
    - Sports Information: 5/16/03 @ 2 PM Studio Football players digital, 2003 May 30; 8.8 MB 18
    - Media and Marketing: 7/29/04 @ 2 PM Football Field shots of new uniforms and players digital, 2004 August 12; 118.4 MB 69
    - Athletics: 11/29 @ 4:45 PM Alumni Turf Field (field hockey field) for photo of football's championshiop team trophy, 2007 November 29; 73.2 MB 17
    - UAlbany Football Practice, 2008 August 22; 126.1 MB 69
    - Ed Delaney, 2008 November 21; 49.6 MB 49
    - trophies, 2009 July 21; 15.0 MB 14
  - Mens Basketball, 2015 February 20-2015 December 22; 3.6; 560
    - DSC_0040.JPG, 2003 December 6; 83.2 MB 50
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; 45.9 MB 19
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; 158.1 MB 132
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; 128.4 MB 114
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; 158.1 MB 132
    - Men's Basketball Game - Army at UAlbany Great Danes, 2003 December 6; 155.7 MB 86
    - Sports Information: 10/29/04 @ 9:45 AM Gym Men's Basketball Team Photo digital, 2004 November 12; 74.1 MB 43
    - Sports Information: 10/21/05 @ 4 PM RACC atrium Men's Basketball Team Photo, 2005 November 7; 25.1 MB 10
    - Media and Marketing: 3/15/06 @ 10:30 AM RACC parking lot Basketball Team Send Off to NCAA in Philadelphia, 2006 March 29; 215.3 MB 100
    - President: Photo session: 4/25/06 @ 1 PM Governor's Mansion Governor greets UAlbany Basketball Team, 2006 May 5; 357.2 MB 163
    - President: 5/8/06 @ 1:30 PM State Legislative Bldg / State Capital Albany Basketball team visits the State Legislature, 2006 May 23; 336.3 MB 96
    - President: 5/8/06 @ 1:30 PM State Legislative Bldg / State Capital Albany Basketball team visits the State Legislature, 2006 May 23; 337.4 MB 98
    - Sports Information: 5/10/06 @ 11:45 AM RACC Basketball Team photo, 2006 May 24; 45.0 MB 17
    - Sports Information: 5/10/06 @ 11:45 AM RACC Basketball Team photo, 2006 May 24; 150.0 MB 20
    - President: 5/10/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Valedictorian Dinner, 2006 May 24; 143.1 MB 48
    - President: 5/11/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Memorandum of Understanding Agreement_ East China Normal University, 2006 May 24; 122.7 MB 61
    - Athletics: 10/18/06 @ 4:30 PM RACC for photo of the Basketball Team, 2006 October 31; 42.9 MB 17
    - Media and Marketing: 3/14/07 @ 2:30 PM Sefcu Arena parking lot Men's basketball send-off / NCAA Tournament, 2007 March 28; 35.7 MB 98
    - Athletics: 10/25/07 @ 3 p.m., SEFCU Arena to take shot Men's Basketball team., 2007 November 7; 27.9 MB 14
    - 694_5972.jpg, 2008 October 6; 3.9 MB 6
    - basketball team, 2008 October 8; 8.0 MB 20
    - basketball team, 2010 October 8; 44.8 MB 17
  - Mens Lacrosse, 2012 July 8-2016 April 18; 3.7; 714
    - Sports Information: 5/9/03 @ 11 AM Lacrosse Field team photo digital, 2003 May 21; 19.1 MB 20
    - Sports Information: 5/9/03 @ 11 AM Lacrosse Field team photo digital, 2003 May 21; 19.1 MB 20
    - Sports Information: 5/14/04 @ 1:30 PM Football Stands Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2004 May 25; 43.1 MB 25
    - Sports Information: 5/14/04 @ 1:30 PM Football Stands Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2004 May 25; 43.1 MB 25
    - Sports Information: 5/12/05 @ 12:30 PM Football bleechers Lacrosse Team Photo digital, 2005 May 25; 34.6 MB 18
    - Athletics: 1/24/08 @ 4:15 PM, UAB Studio for portrait of Lacrosse Assistant Coach and Student Athelete., 2008 January 24; 3.9 MB 15
  - Track, 2012 April 26-2015 April 20; 3.8; 88
    - Sports Information: 12/14/04 @ 4 PM RACC Lobby Indoor Track digital, 2004 December 22; 167.2 MB 123
    - Sports Information: 12/7/05 @ 4 PM RACC Track Team Photo digital, 2005 December 13; 266.8 MB 93
  - Womens Basketball Team, 2012 March 10-2016 April 22; 3.9; 448
    - Sports Information: 10/29/01 @ 2:30 PM RACC Women's Basketball Team Photo digital, 2001 November 9; 96.3 MB 36
    - Sports Information: 7/24/02 @ 12 Noon Dutch Quad Giants/Media Day digital, 2002 August 7; 11.7 MB 26
    - New Hampshire at UAlbany, 2004 February 8; 317.0 MB 230
    - New Hampshire at UAlbany, 2004 February 8; 317.0 MB 230
    - Sports Information: 10/20/05 @ 3 PM P E Gym Women's Basketball Team digital, 2005 November 3; 295.9 MB 117
    - BPG_09, 2009 February 8; 334.1 MB 334
  - Womens Lacrosse, 2016 April 16-2016 April 18; 3.10; 194
    - Sports Information: 1/31/05 @ 9 AM Halfmoon, NY (meet in RACC Parking lot) team photo digital, 2005 February 9; 40.7 MB 18
    - Sports Information: 1/31/06 @ 3:30 pm RACC Women's Lacrosse Team photo, 2006 February 1; 157.2 MB 70
- Campus, 2005 September 23-2016 July 15; 4; 1621
  - Aerials, 2012 February 14-2016 June 28; 4.1; 186
  - Architecture, 2009 May 27-2016 April 25; 4.2; 296
    - Creative Services: Architect supplied photos of Life Sciences Building, 2006 February 22; 169.0 MB 45
    - Media and Marketing: 6/22/06 @ 10 AM New Admin Bldg. Cement truck, 2006 July 6; 2.8 MB 2
    - Media & Marketing: s: exterior shots of new signage around campus. Downtown campus sign New vehicular direction signs around perimeter road (the ones with real stone at bottom) New digital entry way signs State Quad entrance sign, 2006 October 10; 50.3 MB 31
    - Husted Hall Construction, 2008 June 10; 42.2 MB 70
    - Empire and Freedom Quads, 2008 June 18; 59.7 MB 107
    - window replacement, 2009 July 24; 77.3 MB 42
  - Campus, 2005 September 23-2016 July 15; 4.3; 1621
    - Marketing and Special Events: 8/24/00 @ 11 AM new sculpture studio site digital, 2000 August 7; 26.8 MB 43
    - Special Events: 9/29/00 @ 2 PM New Public Saftey Bldg. Ribbon cutting ceremony digital, 2000 September 21; 12.3 MB 20
    - University Relations: 12/1/00 11:30 - 12 Noon CC Ritazza's Coffee Shop grand opening digital, 2000 December 1; 22.2 MB 20
    - Chartwells: 10/10/01 @ 12 noon CC Burger King Ribbon Cutting digital, 2001 October 18; 34.7 MB 30
    - Chartwells: 11/7/02 @ 12 Noon CC Dreidel's Grand Opening digital, 2002 November 8; 20.8 MB 21
    - CCFG: 10/28/02 @ 5:30 PM President's Residence reception for CCFG Board of Directors digital, 2002 November 13; 79.6 MB 59
    - Chartwells: 1/23/03 @ 12 Noon CC Grand Opening digital, 2003 January 28; 67.8 MB 64
    - Chartwells: Photo session: 1/28/03 @ 12 Noon CC Grand Opening digital, 2003 January 28; 43.2 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 8/14/03 @ 2 PM Milne 200 Mural restoration: Holly Fiedler and Mary Betlejeski digital, 2003 August 29; 86.1 MB 71
    - Media and Marketing: 8/14/03 @ 2 PM Milne 200 Mural restoration: Holly Fiedler and Mary Betlejeski digital, 2003 August 29; 86.1 MB 71
    - Media and Marketing: 9/2/03 @ 11 AM Humanities Bldg. and Lecture Center Media Tour of renovated spaces digital, 2003 September 8; 184.8 MB 76
    - Media and Marketing: 9/2/03 @ 11 AM Humanities Bldg. and Lecture Center Media Tour of renovated spaces digital, 2003 September 8; 184.8 MB 76
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 2 PM Hu Bldg renovated classrooms w/ students digital, 2003 September 9; 9.0 MB 8
    - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 2 PM Hu Bldg renovated classrooms w/ students digital, 2003 September 9; 9.0 MB 8
    - Chartwells:; 9/3/03 @ 3:30 PM Indian Quad Stairwell / Fireside Lounge alt. Female managers group pic digital, 2003 September 16; 196.8 MB 30
    - Chartwells:; 9/3/03 @ 3:30 PM Indian Quad Stairwell / Fireside Lounge alt. Female managers group pic digital, 2003 September 16; 196.8 MB 30
    - President: 11/12/03 @ Art Bdlg Hallway painting of KRH digital, 2003 November 27; 26.9 MB 8
    - President: 11/12/03 @ Art Bdlg Hallway painting of KRH digital, 2003 November 27; 26.9 MB 8
    - Media and Marketing: 10/12/04 @ 4:30 PM Milne Hall Milne Renovation Ribbon-cutting ceremony digital, 2004 August 30; 134.8 MB 96
    - Media and Marketing: 10/12/04 @ 4:30 PM Milne Hall Milne Renovation Ribbon-cutting ceremony digital, 2004 August 30; 134.7 MB 96
    - Chartwells: 10/2/04 @ 4:30 - 5 PM CC Dining Hall - "Coop" Kellogg's Cereal Eating Contest / Quads digital, 2004 October 8; 118.3 MB 76
    - Chartwells: 2/15/05 @ 10:30 AM Location: varuous around campus Chartwells operations digital, 2005 February 25; 220.2 MB 126
    - President: 8/25/05 @ 2:30 PM - 4 PM Empire Commons Lobby Empire Commons and Health Center Tour digital, 2005 September 2; 98.4 MB 58
    - President: 8/26/05 @ 9:30 AM -11:30 AM Indian Quad Move-In Morning digital, 2005 September 2; 233.3 MB 133
    - President: photo session: 8/27/05 @ 8:30 PM Location TBA Welcome Candle Lighting Ceremony digital, 2005 September 2; 102.4 MB 66
    - Media and Marketing: 11/21/05 @ 9:30 AM Indian Quad Observation Deck New LED aircraft warning light installation on Carillon Tower digital, 2005 December 5; 94.5 MB 34
    - President: 11/22/05 @ 9 AM SE corner of Podilum Emergency Preparedness Drill digital, 2005 December 5; 97.3 MB 59
    - President: 12/5/05 @ 7 PM St. Vincent's Parish Ctr / 984 Madison Ave. Pine Hills Neighborhood Assoc. w/ Henry Madej, James Anderson, Frank Wiley, Miriam Trementozzi, 2005 December 5; 131.2 MB 40
    - President: 12/8/05 @ 12:00 Noon Alumni House League of Women Voters Luncheon, 2005 December 5; 66.6 MB 31
    - Libraries: Library portrait restoration project / scan 16 negatives/original prints and print (1) 10 X 15 B&W print from each, 2007 January 1; 49.7 MB 17
    - Media & Marketing: 3/12/07 @ 6 PM 1250 Western Ave - Firehouse for photo of Mike Rothschild, Joe Zambone and Fire Chief to be used in Campus Update story., 2007 March 13; 102.4 MB 192
    - UAB: 3/30/07 @ 10:30 AM Campus Center, 2007 March 30; 54.1 MB 38
    - Media & Marketing: 4/3/07 @ 10:45 AM at the Child Research and Study Center at 1535 Western Ave for photo of Lynn Gelzheiser, 2007 April 4; 113.8 MB 108
    - Development Events: 5/8/07 @ 3:30 - 7 PM for Burton Lecture Event 3:30 " 4:20 pm VIP reception - Paterson & Herbst with Deans & Awardees in Arthur Levite Board Room 4:30 " 6:00 pm Lecture & Ceremony at Page Hall Auditorium 6 " 7 pm Reception in Milne Hall Room 200, 2007 May 9; 186.1 MB 272
    - UAlbany Merchandise, 2008 June 7; 14.8 MB 26
    - Health Center_new location, 2008 August 15; 19.3 MB 44
    - Carillon Event, 2008 October 18; 48.5 MB 91
    - courtyard_parent's fountain, 2008 October 18; 19.7 MB 27
    - bus advertising, 2009 February 14; 54.3 MB 37
    - Foundation Board Reception_Husted Hall, 2010 June 17; 58.9 MB 133
    - Fellows Forum 2010, 2010 June 23; 32.0 MB 42
  - East Campus, 2005 October 29-2014 July 8; 4.4; 160
    - Special Events: 6/24/03 @ 11 AM East Campus Cancer Center Groundbreaking digital, 2003 June 26; 30.3 MB 65
    - Special Events: 6/24/03 @ 11 AM East Campus Cancer Center Groundbreaking digital, 2003 June 26; 30.3 MB 65
    - Functional Genomics: 10/18/04 @ 11:30 AM East Campus Wing A / Construction site Scientific Advisory Board Meeting w/ Nobel Laureiates digital, 2004 October 29; 105.6 MB 76
  - Nano Campus, 2006 August 3-2014 June 3; 4.5; 55
  - University Art Museum, 2005 September 23-2015 April 29; 4.6; 62
    - Media and Marketing: 1/15/04 @ 10 AM Art Museum portrait: Sarah Decker digital, 2004 January 30; 102.0 MB 80
    - Media and Marketing: 1/15/04 @ 10 AM Art Museum portrait: Sarah Decker digital, 2004 January 30; 102.0 MB 80
    - President: 5/3/04 @ 11:15 AM Art Museum Presentation of Nigerian Artwork digital, 2004 May 3; 98.7 MB 82
    - President: 5/3/04 @ 11:15 AM Art Museum Presentation of Nigerian Artwork digital, 2004 May 3; 98.7 MB 82
    - President: 4/27/04 @ 6 PM CC Patroon Room Fudan University Delegation digital, 2004 May 3; 196.0 MB 120
    - MesoAmerican Studies: 9/29/04 @ 2:30 PM Art Museum NYLARNet Reception digital, 2004 October 7; 101.8 MB 70
    - President's Office: 2/2/05 @ 3:30 - 5:30 PM Art Museum Hail and Farewell digital, 2005 February 3; 275.3 MB 157
    - Media and Marketing: 6/15/05 @ 3:30 PM Art Museum Julie Maliszewski / intern digital, 2005 June 29; 97.5 MB 67
    - Media and Marketing: 10/3/06 @ 3 PM Art Museum International Students and Faculy Reception, 2006 October 3; 36.1 MB 18
    - Denis Hayes tours Art Museum, 2009 February 10; 38.1 MB 53
- CommunityEngagement, 2012 November 14-2016 July 13; 5; 1320
  - CommunityEngagement, 2012 November 14-2016 July 13; 5.1; 1320
    - Marketing and Outreach: 10/14/00 @ 10 AM Collins Circle Race for Literacy digital, 2000 October 19; 28.3 MB 44
    - Social Welfare: 2/21/02 @ 11:30 AM Westview Senior Center Central Ave / Allen St. Students working with seniors color print, 2002 February 25; 28.0 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 9/11/03 @ 3:20 PM Hamilton and Quail Sts. Albany students w/community neighbors in Pine Hills digital, 2003 September 25; 139.0 MB 77
    - Media and Marketing: 9/11/03 @ 3:20 PM Hamilton and Quail Sts. Albany students w/community neighbors in Pine Hills digital, 2003 September 25; 139.0 MB 77
    - Media and Marketing: 10/7/03 @ 12 Noon Phillip Schuyler Elementary School (next to downtown campus) elementary school kids with garden produce digital, 2003 October 16; 150.8 MB 56
    - Media and Marketing: 10/7/03 @ 12 Noon Phillip Schuyler Elementary School (next to downtown campus) elementary school kids with garden produce digital, 2003 October 16; 150.8 MB 56
    - Outreach: 11/13/03 @ 1:15 PM Capital Repertory Theater Lobby Martha Rozette w/ Jiff Rafferty digital, 2003 November 24; 37.5 MB 30
    - Outreach: 11/13/03 @ 1:15 PM Capital Repertory Theater Lobby Martha Rozette w/ Jiff Rafferty digital, 2003 November 24; 37.5 MB 30
    - Outreach: 12/1/03 @ 10 AM Delmar Reformed Church shots of large class of adult students digital, 2003 November 28; 56.3 MB 33
    - Outreach: 12/3/03 @ 1:30 PM Delmar Reformed Church Prof. John Delano with adult students digital, 2003 November 28; 43.8 MB 32
    - Outreach: 12/1/03 @ 10 AM Delmar Reformed Church shots of large class of adult students digital, 2003 November 28; 56.3 MB 33
    - Outreach: 12/3/03 @ 1:30 PM Delmar Reformed Church Prof. John Delano with adult students digital, 2003 November 28; 43.8 MB 32
    - Outreach: 8/18/04 @ 11 AM 30 S. Pearl St. CIFA Sanjay Goel, Laura Iwan, and Tom Hurbanek digital, 2004 September 1; 26.9 MB 15
    - Outreach: 8/18/04 @ 11 AM 30 S. Pearl St. CIFA Sanjay Goel, Laura Iwan, and Tom Hurbanek digital, 2004 September 1; 26.9 MB 15
    - Outreach: 11/30/04 @ 3 PM Albany YMCA Washington Ave. Students: digital, 2004 December 2; 44.8 MB 30
    - Media and Marketing: 4/4/05 @ TBA Amsterdam, NY Center for eht Elimination of Minority Health Disparities digital, 2005 April 5; 159.2 MB 129
    - Media and Marketing: 6/8/05 @ 11 AM Cititzen's Bank cor of Western and West Lawrence Albany, NY Mayor's Mid-town College Employer Assisted Housing Program digital, 2005 June 20; 141.4 MB 82
    - Media and Marketing: 12/2/05 @ 11:45 AM CC Assembly Hall Albany High School Students digital, 2005 December 15; 286.8 MB 60
    - University Development: 1/9/06 @ 1:30 pm Albany High School Albany, NY HS students: Angali Francis, Thanasi Athanassiadis, Naketa Jones, and Regina Taylor, 2006 January 23; 74.1 MB 35
    - Development: 10/24/06 @ Kermit Hall Memorial Tree Planting in West Garden (area between Library and Social Science Building), 2006 October 24; 13.9 MB 9
    - Media & Marketing: 4/24/07 @ 11 AM Indian Quad for Campus Clean Up Day photo of Susan Herbst and coaches planting trees; then other general shots of staff working., 2007 April 24; 89.8 MB 87
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/6/08 @ 11:30 a.m. for Campus Cleanup between State Quad and the podium., 2008 May 6; 46.1 MB 59
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 5/6/08 @ 11:30 a.m. for Campus Cleanup between State Quad and the podium., 2008 May 6; 46.1 MB 59
    - Longfield Farm_Gary Kleppel and Erin LaBarge, 2008 July 20; 360.3 MB 136
    - Leaders in Service Program_habitat_for_humanity, 2008 July 23; 103.4 MB 44
    - Habitat for Humanity_Chinese students, 2009 March 28; 94.4 MB 72
    - Lego Expo, 2010 February 5; 215.6 MB 235
      2016 December 20 Submission Information Package (SIP) created with createSIP.py version 0.1
  - University Police Department, 2012 November 14-2016 January 17; 5.2; 212
    - Media and Marketing: 9/12/03 @ 3:30 PM Cobblestone area at Collins Circle 5 Quad: students w/ ambulance digital, 2003 September 16; 26.9 MB 11
    - Media and Marketing: 9/12/03 @ 3:30 PM Cobblestone area at Collins Circle 5 Quad: students w/ ambulance digital, 2003 September 16; 26.9 MB 11
    - Media and Marketing: 3/24/05 @ 6:30 PM Hall of Fame Room RACC Pres. Hall addresses annual UPD Awards digital, 2005 April 7; 84.2 MB 50
    - Media and Marketing: 3/29/05 @ 1:15 PM Facilities Management Pres Hall meets staff, 2005 April 12; 69.4 MB 48
    - President: 9/29/05 @ 3 PM Standish Rm Swearing-in Ceremony 2 new police officers digital, 2005 October 14; 36.5 MB 25
    - Media & Marketing: 11/8/07 from 10 - 2 at the Campus Center Ballroom to take shots of FBI challenges UAlbany students, for In the News., 2007 November 20; 61.1 MB 111
    - Media & Markeeting: 11/19/07 from 2 - 4 pm to take publicity shots for ESOL class located in grouds bldg next to UPD., 2007 November 21; 24.4 MB 65
    - UPD_Train the Trainer, 2008 August 21; 35.1 MB 80
    - UPD_Ed Myers and Bianca, 2010 April 7; 33.1 MB 43
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6; 22929
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6.1; 22929
    - Unknown Event, 1999 February 26; 6.7 MB 11
    - Unknown Event in Campus Center, 1999 April 9; 6.2 MB 10
    - Awards Ceremony in Campus Center Ballroom, 1999 April 10; 16.3 MB 24
    - Health Management: 10/18/00 @ 8 am Nurse's Assoc. Albany Breakfast session digital, 2000 September 11; 18.9 MB 30
    - Health Management: 9/29/00 @ 9 am Alumni House seminar digital, 2000 September 26; 10.8 MB 17
    - University Relations: 9/15/00 @ 2 pm State Education Bldg. 2nd Floor Albany "College to Work Program" Commissioner Richard Mills with President Hitchcock digital image, 2000 September 27; 15.6 MB 24
    - Health Management: 11/30/00 @ 9 am Alumni House conference- keynote speaker digital, 2000 December 11; 15.9 MB 12
    - Health Management: 2/6/00 @ 8:15 am Nurses' Assoc. Latham Legislative Update Breakfast digital, 2000 December 19; 22.9 MB 14
    - NYS Writer's Institute: 1/22/00 @ 3:30 PM State Author/Poet Award Ceremony Capitol Bldg/ Red Room / Kurt Vonnegut 1/22/00 @ 5 PM reception Elda's on Lark St. Photo session 1/22/00 @ 7 PM Public Reading/Reception Page Hall color print, 2001 January 5; 149.8 MB 91
    - Advancement: 1/22/01 @ 9:30 Dewey Library Downtown Campus press conference/financial aid scams, 2001 February 2; 20.7 MB 12
    - University Relations: 1/31/01 @ 11 AM Lecture Center Concourse Community Service Fair digital, 2001 February 9; 19.5 MB 13
    - photo Session: 2/15/00 @ 6pm PAC? Reception: Congressman John Lewis color print, 2001 March 28; 156.5 MB 63
      2016 December 14 Original job number incorrect, changed 20000935 to 20001244
    - University Relations: 3/15/01 @ 4:15 PM LC-23 Carl H. Rosner at the podium digital, 2001 March 29; 24.2 MB 21
    - Univesity Relations: 3/19/01 @ 3 PM MSB-200 Rosyln Jefferson digital, 2001 April 3; 41.8 MB 37
    - University Relations: 9/12/01 @ Collins Circle/CC Fountain Unity Walk, 2001 September 26; 93.0 MB 77
    - University Relations: 9/21/01 @ 12:30 RACC Memorial Service digital and color print, 2001 October 5; 151.9 MB 86
    - Advancement: 10/30/01 @ 8 AM Standish Room Business Matter debut taping w/ Dick Highfield digital?, 2001 November 5; 7.4 MB 4
    - Advancement: 1/9/02 @ 7:15 AM Crowne Plaza Hotel Albany Boosting Business in NY State w/ Elliot Spitzer digital, 2002 January 1; 45.8 MB 46
    - Health Management: 1/15/02 @ 8 AM NYS Nurses Assoc. Latham digital imagery, 2002 January 22; 54.9 MB 44
    - Media and Marketing: 3/6/02 @ 2 - 3 PM CC Ballroom Public Interest Career Fair digital, 2002 March 18; 43.2 MB 36
    - Annual Fund: 3/12/02 @ 6:30 PM Annual Fund Telemarketing Room web shots digital, 2002 March 25; 63.0 MB 52
    - Media and Marketing: 3/14/02 @ 2 PM - 3/15/02 @ 12 Noon CC Ballroom "Leave no child behind" Conference Henry Louis Taylor / Terrence Thornberry digital, 2002 March 29; 62.1 MB 51
    - Stewardship: 4/11/02 @ 1 - 2 PM BA 231 Towers Perrin Gift announcement digital, 2002 April 4; 84.8 MB 76
    - Media and Marketing: 4/1/02 @ 12:00 Noon East Campus document signing: SUNY and EPA digital, 2002 April 15; 44.9 MB 39
    - Media and Marketing: 4/3/02 @ 10:30 AM State Capital Bldg. Harriman Campus Press Conference digital, 2002 April 17; 58.8 MB 49
    - Media and Marketing: 4/4/02 @ 10 AM CC Assembly Hall Ribbon Cutting Ceremony: Internet 2 digital, 2002 April 17; 12.6 MB 11
    - Media and Marketing: Photo session: 4/22/02 @ 10:15 AM Library Atrium Organ and Tissue Donar Event digital, 2002 April 22; 87.0 MB 73
    - Outreach: 4/10/02 @ 11 AM Downtown Albany - behind City Hall 350 Years Celebration digital, 2002 April 24; 88.9 MB 70
    - Media and Marketing: 4/9/02 State Legislative Bldg. / Albany Wall of Difference digital, 2002 April 24; 20.4 MB 17
    - Media and Marketing: 4/30/02 @ 11 AM Albany Marriott - Wolf Rd. Tech Valley Summit w/ Tom Brokaw digital, 2002 May 8; 77.6 MB 70
    - Media and Marketing: 4/30/02 @ 2 pm New Library Atrium IFW founding members digital, 2002 May 14; 16.4 MB 14
    - Media and Marketing: 5/16/02 @ 4 PM - Milne 200 Burton Lecture Series: Katherine Bertini color print, 2002 May 17; 213.8 MB 127
    - UA Outreach: 6/10/02 @ 11 AM Library - Standish Room Jewish Center Conference digital, 2002 June 24; 19.9 MB 18
    - Advancement: 7/26/02 @ 7:30 AM Giant's VIP Breakfast digital images, 2002 June 26; 23.9 MB 60
    - Special Events: 9/26/02 @ 2 PM Barnes & Noble Room / Atrium Level New Library Barnes & Noble Bookstore Scholarship Reception digital, 2002 August 28; 168.5 MB 64